A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976-1985.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files, 1974-1985 (Accession 37778)., Extent: x cubic feet (x boxes)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Office - Cabinet meetings / People's Day, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Office - General, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Office - News conferences and press releases, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Office - Speeches and remarks, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Local Advisory Committee, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Golden, Ken, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Hill, Elva (Fiscal Services / General Services), 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: House Appropriations Committee, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: House Appropriations Committee - Presentations, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: House Finance Committee, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Health, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education, State Council of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: House of Delegates, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Human Resources, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: ID Card Committee, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Industrial Development, Division of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislative Implementation Reports, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislative tour - New members, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislative tracking, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Libraries, White House Conference on, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Loan schedules - Dept. of Accounts, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Local Government Advisory Countil, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Local Government Officials Conference, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Manson, Jennifer Joy, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Miscellaneous, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Murphy, Larry, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO), 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO) - Executive Committee, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO) - Southern Regional Meeting, 1979 June. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: National Tax Association / Tax Institute of America (NTA/TIA), 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: National Governors' Association, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: National Association of Tax Administrators, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Planning District Commissions, Virginia Association of, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Professions Committee, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Program Proposals and Targeting - Retreat, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Public Safety, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Purchase and Supply, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Revenue Collections, Estimates and Transfer Statements (Dept. of Acconts), 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Revenue Reports and Presentation to the General Assembly, 1978. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Revenue Resources and Economic Commission, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Revenue Sharing, Office of, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Salary Survey, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Senate, U.S. - Committee on Finance, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Senate Bill 28 Task Force, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Senate Finance Committee, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Sheriff's Association, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Social Security Administration, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Area Chambers of Commerce meeting, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Southeastern Association of Tax Administrators (SEATA), 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Southeastern Association of Tax Administration (SEATA) - Executive Committee, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: State Aid to Localities, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: State Tax Review, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Tax Administrator News, 1979. (Box 53)
  - Retirement System, Virginia Supplemental, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Retrocession - Norfolk Naval Base, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Reynolds, J. Sargeant, Community College, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Savings Bond Campaign, U.S., 1979. (Box 54)
  - Second Injury Fund, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Ship Building, Governor's Task Force on, 1979. (Box 54)
  - SJR 58 - Authority to State Agencies, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Small Business Development Centers Task Force, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1979. (Box 55)
  - State Fair, Virginia, 1979. (Box 55)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Telecommunications Study Commission, 1979. (Box 55)
  - United Nations, 1979. (Box 55)
  - University of Virginia, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Urban Assistance Incentive Fund, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Virginia Associated Research Campus, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University / Medical College of Virginia, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University / Medical College of Virginia - Health Sciences Division, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Virginia State College, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Virginia Telecommunications Council, 1979. (Box 55)
  - Virginia Water Project, Inc., 1979. (Box 55)
  - VISTA grants, 1978-1979. (Box 55)
  - War Veterans Claims, Reassignment of, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Water Control Board, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Welfare, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Welfare, Dept. of - Locan Group Homes, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Western State Hospital - Properties, 1976-1978. (Box 54)
  - William and Mary, College of, 1979. (Box 54)
  - Legislation, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Legislation - Federal, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Legislation - Virginia, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Legislative Coordination and Clearance Procedures, 1978-1979. (Box 56)
  - Legislators - State (correspondence), 1979. (Box 56)
  - Liaison Office, 1978-1979. (Box 56)
  - Local Government Advisory Commission, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of - Internal Audits, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Management Development Institute, Commonwealth, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Management Support Program - Review and Evaluation, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Marijuana - Paraquat testing, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Memos to agencies, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation Institutions, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Metric conversion, 1979. (Box 56)
  - ,Miscellaneous correspondence 1979. (Box 56)
  - Motor Vehicles, Division of, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 56)
  - ,Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Cost for salary regrades 1979. (Box 57)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Employee Performance Evaluation Policy, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Grievance procedures, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Health insurance, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Intergovernmental Personnel Act, 1979. (Box 56)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Personnel decentralization, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - President's Wage and Price Standards, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Salary scales / Salary surveys, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Program budgeting, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Property records and insurance, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Property records and insurance - Flood insurance for state properties, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Property records and insurance - Liability insurance, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Property records and insurance - Liability project, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Property records and insurance - State motor vehicle fleet, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Proposition 13 - Virginia proposals, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Public Building Commission, 1978. (Box 57)
  - Public Building Commission, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Purchases and Supply, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Purchases and Supply, Dept. of - Printing, stationary, etc., 1979. (Box 57)
  - Purchases and Supply, Dept. of - Task Force, 1979. (Box 57)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Accounts, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Accounting Office (DPB Budget), 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Administration and Finance, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Aging, Office on, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Agriculture and Commerce, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Analysis of alternatives, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Attorney General, Office of the, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Aviation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Biennium preparation (1980-1982 Biennium), 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Bills and resolutions requiring executive agency action, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Bills the Governor has not signed into law (fact sheet), 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Bills which have fiscal impact statements and passed both houses, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Hearing (1980-1982 Biennium), 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - HJR and SJR with Budget/Fiscal Implications, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Interim Bud System Redesign Project, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Planning and Budget bill signed by the Governor, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Program budgeting, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Program exhibits, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Budget Summary (1978-1980 Biennium - amended by 1979 General Assembly), 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget - Targeting (1980-1982 Biennium), 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budgeting Guidance, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Calendar, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Capital Outlay, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Capital Outlay - Reapportion for 1980-1982, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Capital Outlay - Requests, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: CARS, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Central appropriations, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Christopher Newport College, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Commerce and Resources, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Community Colleges, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Computer Services, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Connock, Stuart - Memos sent out, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Consolidated Laboratory Services, Div. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Corrections, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Criminial Justice Services, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Crockin, Ed, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Directives (DPB), 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Eastern Virginia Medical Authority, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Education, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Education, Dept. of - Local impact funds, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Education, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 58)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Emergency and Energy Services, Office of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Employee Position Report, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Employee Relations Counselors, Office of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Engineering and Buildings, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Expenditure classifications, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Federal Budget (1980) - Fiscal impact for Virginia, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Federal grants, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Format - Budget, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: General Services, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: George Mason University, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Goals, objectives and policies, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Golden, Ken, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Office - Executive, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Handicapped requirements - Sec. 504, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Health, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education Institutions, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education Institutions - Advertising, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education Institutions - Architectural barriers, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education Institutions - Auxilliary Enterprise Operations, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education Institutions - Faculty salaries, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education Institutions - Non-general funds, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Higher Education Institutions - Overhead Reserve Funds, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Highways and Transportation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Historic Landmarks Commission, Virginia, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Housing, Office of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Housing - Policies for Rental structures for state owned property, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Howard, Ken - Study report, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Human Resources, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Industrial Development, Division of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: James Madison University, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Justice and Crime Prevention, Division of, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislation, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislation, 1980. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislation - Summary of Proposed, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislative coordination, 1979. (Box 59)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Legislative Services, Division of, 1979. (Box 59)